[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
>> Good afternoon everybody!
>> 大家下午好
Welcome to WWDC2017.
欢迎来到 WWDC 2017
My name is David Duncan.
我叫 David Duncan
I'll be joined by Raj Ramamurphy
今天  我将和 Raj Ramamurphy
[phonetic] and Kyle Sluder
还有 Kyle Sluder 一起
[phonetic].
讲一讲
about updating your app for iOS
怎么更新你的 app
11.
来适配 iOS 11
So first a little agenda for
首先说一下
what we're going to talk about
我们今天
today.
都要讲些什么
The first thing that I'm going
第一个要和你们
to be discussing with you is
讨论的事情是
adopting new functionality in UI
如何在 UI 设计套件里
kits bars; UI navigation bar, UI
启用新功能
tab bar, UI toolbar, and UI
包括 UI 导航栏 UI 标签栏
search bar.
UI 工具栏和 UI 搜索栏
And we're going to talk to you
我们会告诉你
about how these can update your
这些如何能够使你的 app
app to the new looks that we've
变成我们在介绍 iOS 11 时
introduced throughout iOS 11.
你所看到的那样
Next Kyle will come up and talk
然后 Kyle 会上来
to you a bit about managing
给你们讲一讲
margins and insets, changes that
如何调整边缘和嵌入
we've made to UI scroll view and
以及我们对 UI scroll view 和 table view
table view will come after that,
做出的改变
and we're going to use all that
我们会教你
to show you how you can make
如何利用这些新功能
your app better.
让你的 app 变得更棒
So let's start by taking a look
首先  我们来看一看
at the files app.
文件夹
So if you've gotten the chance
如果你安装了
to install the beta and take a
Beta 版
look at the files app, you'll
并看了文件夹
see some changes that it's
你会发现它利用 UI 设计套件
taking advantage of from UI kit.
做出的一些改变
You can see that giant, large
你可以看到上面的
title view up there showing the
这些大标题
browse feature.
显示出浏览功能
You've got a search bar right
它下面
below it that has a bit of a
有个搜索栏
different appearance from any
这个搜索栏
search bar you've probably seen
应该和你之前看到过的
before.
都不太一样
Now the tab bar actually has
标签栏也有一些变化
some changes, but you won't see
但是这里看不出来
them here so let's go ahead and
所以让我们
rotate this to landscape.
变成横屏
We've got this brand new
标签栏
appearance for the tab bar, both
在横屏和 iPad 里
in landscape and on iPad, where
都采用了新的外观
we show the icon and the text
图标和文字
side by side.
并排显示
And in particular on iPhones the
尤其是在 iPhone 里
icon is smaller and the tab bar
图标变小了
is smaller to give a bit more
标签栏也小了一些
room vertically.
使得纵向有更多空间
We're going to discuss how you
我们会告诉你
can customize the icons for
如何个性化
landscape and tab bar as well.
横屏和标签栏的图标
Now things getting smaller can
变小之后
sometimes be a problem for users
有时会对
that are hard of vision or
视力较弱
otherwise need a little
或者需要借助帮助
assistance to see things
才能看清的人
clearer.
产生一定影响
We've got you covered there too.
这个我们也可以解决
If you turn on larger text then
如果你选择更大的字体
when you long press on one of
当你长按这些
these items -- this is in tab
无论是标签栏  工具栏
bar, tool bar, and navigation
还是导航栏
bar -- we'll put up this HUD
都会出现这个 HUD
that shows you clearly what the
会清晰的显示
text is and what the icon is.
文字和图标
And now I'm going to explain how
接下来我要介绍
both of these features can be
如何在你的 app 里
adopted in your app and they're
使用这两项功能
really, really easy.
非常容易
So there's this class called UI
有一个分类叫 UI Bar Item
Bar Item that you probably never
你可能没怎么注意过
thought much about because it's
因为它其实是
actually the super class of two
UI 设计套件中
important bar item classes in UI
两个重要 class 的上级目录
kit; UI tab bar item and UI bar
分别是 UI Tab Bar Item
button item.
和 UI Bar Button Item
And so to customize the image in
要想个性化
landscape on that tab bar all
标签栏在横屏的显示
you have to do is set this
你只需要把这个属性
property, the landscape image
这个 Landscape Image Phone 的属性
phone property, on any UI tab
加入你想
bar items that you're placing in
放入标签栏的
your tab bars.
任何一个标签项中
And of course we'll have support
当然在 storyboard 和其他地方
for this in storyboards and
我们都有相关支持
everywhere else, but that's how
但这就是
you would customize that.
个性化的方法
And there are also some inset
还有一些
properties in case you need
嵌入属性
those.
你可以选择
For that HUD image we've got
要显示 HUD
another related property called
也有一个相关的属性
the Large Content Size Image.
叫 Large Content Size Image
Now you can set this, put a big
你可以设置这个
image in there, it'll appear in
输入大图标
the HUD, but if you're using PDF
就会显示在 HUD 里  当然如果
assets in your asset catalogue
你的资源目录里使用的是 PDF 的话
it's even easier.
就更简单了
All you have to do is set that
你只需要设定
preserve PDF data and we'll
保存 PDF 数据
automatically pick up the PDF
我们就能自动提取这个 PDF 数据
data, resize it larger, and
调整大小
display it in that HUD without
并在 HUD 中显示
you having to do anything to
而你完全不需要
your assets.
做其他任何事情
So if you wanted to learn more
如果你想了解更多
about accessibility features
辅助功能
such as the HUD and how you can
比如 HUD 以及使用方法
pick that up, there's the What's
这周三
New in Accessibility session
有专门关于辅助功能
happening this Wednesday.
的讲座
I recommend you go there to
建议你们可以去听一听
learn all about what's new in
iOS 11 中
accessibility in iOS 11.
新的辅助功能
And so let's talk next about
接下来我们聊聊
navigation bar.
导航栏
How do we get those large titles
我们怎么让这些大标题
that appeared in the files app
显示在文件夹上
and other apps across the
和系统里的
system?
其他 app 上
So first there's a new property
首先  UI 导航栏
on UI navigation bar, prefers
有个新的属性
large titles.
叫 prefers Large Titles
If you set this to "true" on any
在任何一个导航栏
given navigation bar then you'll
设定为 true
start seeing large titles all
你就可以在各个系统
across the system -- all across
和各个 app 里
your application.
看到大标题
Now you might be wondering; what
你可能在想
do these other three words that
这一页上的
I've got here on this slide --
另外三个词
maybe they're a little hard to
可能有点看不清
see, but automatic, always, and
Automatic  Always  Never
never -- what does that have to
这三个词
do with?
是干嘛的
Well, there's a second property
当他们出现时
to control when these appear;
有另一个属性可以控制
the large title display mode.
叫 large Title Display Mode
This is what easily allows you
它可以让你轻松的
to determine for each view
控制
control you push onto a nav
在每个 Navigation Controller
controller or to a navigation
和导航栏 stack
bar stack when the large title
是否让大标题
appears.
出现
And let me show you how that
现在让我来
works.
告诉你们怎么做
So we turned on large titles on
我们在这个导航栏中
this navigation bar and we put
打开大标题
an item on there.
然后在上面放一个条目
It defaults to automatic and
它会默认为 Automatic
automatic means whatever the
意味着
current state is, whoever asked
现有状态
last for that bar to appear,
无论谁执行了该操作
keep it.
都会自动保存
Since nothing else is on the
现在这个 stack 上没有别的
stack and we turned on large
所以当我们选择大标题
titles, we have a large title.
大标题就出现了
But let's go ahead and push a
但是如果我们选中
navigation item that we don't
一个不希望显示大标题的
want to display that large title
Navigation Item
on and we just set the large
我们只需要把 large Title Display Mode
title display mode to "never"
选为 never
and the large title goes away.
大标题就消失了
Now again we'll push an
现在我们重新选择
"automatic," preserve whatever
Automatic
we have now, and so we don't get
保存现有设置
a large title, and then we'll
就没有大标题了
push "always," and now the large
但如果这时选择 Always
title is back.
大标题又回来了
And again, we can push an
这时再选择 Automatic
"automatic" and we're all there.
一切就又保存成这样了
Simple. So there are two more
很简单
things we want to talk about on
关于 Navigation Item
navigation item and the first is
还有两件事要说
how to integrate the search
第一是
controller and the new search
如何在导航栏上
bar look with your navigation
结合 Search Controller
bars.
和新的搜索栏
There's a single property again,
有另一个简单的属性
navigation item search
叫 Navigation Item Search Controller
You assign your search
只要把 Search Controller
controller to the navigation
分配给 Navigation Item
item and you're done.
就可以了
The search bar is placed
搜索栏出现在正确的位置上
correctly and it behaves just as
看起来和我们其他
it does in a lot of our apps.
很多 app 里的一样
Now if you've actually gotten a
如果你有机会
chance to play with "files" or
探索过文件夹
"mail" or some of the others
邮件或者其他一些 app
you'll notice that sometimes
你会发现有时候
that search bar stays pegged
搜索栏会保持不动
when you scroll, sometimes it
当你滑动页面时
does not.
搜索栏不会跟着滑动
In particular in "files" it
尤其是在文件夹中
stays pegged and that's
搜索栏会固定位置
controlled by this "hide search
这是由 hides Search Bar when Scrolling
bar when scrolling" property.
这个属性控制的
It defaults to "true."
它默认为 true
So, for example in "mail" it
所以在邮件里它会
scrolls away, but in "files"
随着滑动而移动
they've turned it off.
但在文件夹里这个属性被关闭了
And so it stays pegged.
所以搜索栏就停留在页面上了
You can always reach the search
你可以随时搜索
bar and it looks great.
这看起来很棒
So how does all this work?
这是怎么做到的
A little bit of behind the
我来告诉你们
scenes on some of these things.
一些小技巧
And the first thing you should
首先
know is that a lot of these
你要了解
interactions are actually
很多类似的交互
mediated by UI navigation
是由 UI Navigation Controller
controller.
控制的
So if you're taking the
所以如果你
navigation bar and assembling
在导航栏
kind of the entire push and pop
自己汇编这些指令
experience yourself, and not
并不是很多人会这么做
many people do, but if you are
不过如果你做了
you're not going to get some of
你就无法得到
these features.
现在的某些性能
In particular you're not going
尤其是没办法
to get the search controller
做到 Search Controller
integration.
的融合
You're not going to get refresh
你没办法做到
controls hoisting and you're not
提升 Refresh control
going to get rubber bending.
也无法做到 Rubber bending
Rubber bending is when you start
Rubber bending 指的是
pulling down, that large title
当你下拉时
grows larger, and responds to
大标题变大
that scroller.
并随着滚动条移动
So that's navigation bar,
这些就是关于导航栏
navigation controller, and those
Navigation Controller
new large title features.
和大标题的介绍
But while we're here making all
当我们做出这些调整时
of these changes we figured
我们想
let's actually make some other
不如再做些别的变化
changes to help your lives be
能够让你们
easier as well.
使用的更加方便
And so now in iOS 11, UI toolbar
所以现在在 iOS 11 里
and UI navigation bar both have
UI 工具栏和导航栏
intricate and express support
都有很多功能
for auto layout.
来完成自动布局
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
So what this means is that your
这意味着
custom bar button items, your
个性化 Bar Button Items
custom title of use, can now use
和个性化 title views
layout to express their size to
可以使用自动布局
us and get the proper layout
来调整大小
that you would otherwise expect.
从而达到你想要的状态
Now there are a few things to
还有几件事情
keep in mind.
希望你们能记住
One of them is you kind of want
一个是
to keep your constraints inside
把约束项
of that view.
保持在 view 里面
So if you give us a custom title
所以当你设定个性化 view
view you want to make sure that
你要注意
any constraints there only
所有的约束项
reference that title view and
只指向某一个 title view
any of its sub-views.
和它的 sub-view
And this one is kind of big, but
另一个有些大
it's kind of worth bringing out,
但是也值得一提
is that when you use auto layout
当你使用自动布局时
we also assume you know what
我们是假设
you're doing [laughter] and the
你知道自己在做什么的  [ 笑 ]
reason why I bring this up is
之所以要说这个
because otherwise you end up in
是因为我不希望
this case where you have to --
你们会遇到这种情况
you get zero sized views.
Zero-Sized view
So how do you avoid these zero
怎么才能不出现
sized views?
Zero-Sized view 呢
Well, UI navigation bar and UI
UI 导航栏
toolbar provide positioning
和 UI 工具栏
information.
提供位置信息
Zero sized views end up becoming
之所以会出现 Zero-Size view
because you have some ambiguous
是因为布局中
constraint layout.
有不明确的约束项
And so the position is taken
所以空间被
care of for you.
自动填补了
You won't get your views shoved
你的 view 不会
up in an upper left corner
缩小到左上角
somewhere, but you still have to
但是你依然需要
provide sizing for us.
给我们提供一个尺寸
And there are three ways you can
有三种方法
do that.
可以做到
You could add constraints for
你可以为宽和高
width and height; perfectly
添加约束项
legal, perfectly legitimate.
非常合理
Do that. You can put whatever
你还可以把
else you want in there and
其他你想要的条件写入
you're golden.
就完美了
You could also implement
你也可以使用
intrinsic content size.
Intrinsic Content Size
That'll also give us as much
这也为我们
information as we need.
提供了足够的信息
You go along with the content
你可以进行
compression hugging and
限制内容变大
compression resistance and
和变小的设置
you're set.
这样就行了
But finally, the most easy way,
最后  当然也是最简单的
for most people, is to actually
对于大多数人来说
make sure that all of your
你只要确保你的
sub-views are properly connected
所有 sub-view
and set up with auto layout.
都关联到自动布局
And what that means is let's say
也就是说
you have a custom title view and
比如你有一个想个性化的标题
you have a label and a button in
里面有一个标签和一个按键
there, if you want to make sure
如果你想
that you get the proper
有一个合适的
horizontal width of that title
水平宽度
view you just need to make sure
你只需要确保
that there are constraints set
标签和按键之间
up between those labels and
有设定好的约束值
buttons such that the leading
这样在这两个 view 中
and trailing edge, or the width,
标题的前沿后沿
of that title view is defined in
以及宽度
terms of those two views.
就都设定好了
And so that's how you can use
这就是如何
auto layout to add precise
利用自动布局
control to the size of your
为你个性化的
custom title views and bar
标题和条目
button items.
调整大小
Now, to demonstrate all the
接下来
things we've talked about today
为了演示我们刚才说的内容
we bring up Raj Ramamurphy to
让我们邀请 Raj Ramamurphy
give you a demo.
给你们进行演示
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
>> Thanks David.
>> 谢谢 David
So as David just explained, we
就像 David 刚才说的
have a bunch of great new API in
我们在 iOS 11 里
iOS 11 for these new, large
为这些新的导航栏
navigation bars.
添加了很多很棒的新 API
I'm going to walk you through
我要告诉你们
updating an app for iOS 11.
如何更新 app 来适配 iOS 11
So here's a sample app we're
今天
going to be working with today.
我的例子
It's a pretty simple app called
是个很简单的 app
"Trail Diary."
叫 Trail Diary
It's just a diary of some trails
是一个访问轨迹
I visited.
的日志
So here we are in the main view
这是主 View Controller
controller, which I called the
我称它为
"memory view controller."
Memory View Controller
Now, if I tap on one of these
如果我点中一个条目
cells you'll notice I get a
你会发现
detail view controller.
这是 Detail View Controller
This contains a photo, a
包含一张照片
description, and some
一个描述
information about this.
和一些信息
There's also a way to add
还有一种方法
comments, and we're going to get
可以添加评论
into that a little bit later,
我们一会儿会讲到
but for now let's start updating
但是现在让我们
this app for iOS 11.
先更新这个 app
One of the first things I'd like
首先要介绍
to do is introduce support in
在这个 app 里
this application for those
为这些漂亮的大标题
beautiful, new large titles.
提供支持
So let's go ahead and do that.
让我们开始吧
We'll go over to the navigation
我们打开 Navigation
-- or sorry -- to the memory
对不起
view controller here and we're
Memory View Controller
going to get the navigation
输入
controller.
Navigation Controller
Get the navigation bar and set
然后是 navigation bar
the "prefers large titles"
把 prefers Large Titles 属性
property on the navigation bar.
设定给导航栏
Now, when we set this property
当你设定了这个属性
we get large titles everywhere.
所有地方都变成大标题了
And if I recompile and rerun the
如果我重新编译
application, head back over to
并重启这个 app
it, and bring up the memory view
重新打开 Memory View Controller
controller you'll notice we have
你可以看到
this beautiful, large title, and
这个漂亮的大标题
since we already have a refresh
因为我们已经把
control that gets hoisted into
Refresh control 设置到
the navigation bar and we get
导航栏了
the rubber banding experience --
我们就可以看到 Rubber banding
everything's looking great.
一切看起来都很棒
Now, "prefers large titles" will
Prefers Large Titles 会让所有地方
turn large titles on everywhere.
都变成大标题
So if I tap back into the detail
所以如果我回到
view controller you'll see we
Detail View Controller
get a really nice transition and
可以看到一个很漂亮的过渡
we have the detail view
Detail View Controller 里
controller showing a large title
也显示出
as well.
大标题了
Now this is great, but sometimes
这很好  但是有时
the large title isn't what you
你并不希望
want everywhere.
大标题出现在所有地方
And so for that, as David
所以就像 David 说的
explained, we have the
我们有一个
navigation item property, "large
Navigation Item 属性
title display mode."
Large title Display Mode
So in this view I'd like to show
我希望在这个 view 里显示
the standard inline title.
标准的行内标题
So let's update this view
让我们来更新这个 View Controller
controller to show that.
来显示行内标题
If I go over to the detail view
打开 Detail View Controller
controller and set its
把 Navigation Item 的
navigation items' large title
Large Title Display Mode
display mode to "never," as
设定为 never
David showed you before with the
就像 David 之前用 stack 展示的那样
stack, if we recompile and rerun
如果我们再编译并重启 app
the application, we'll start out
我们一开始会看到
with the large title, but if I
大标题
push view controller now we have
但是如果我点中 View Controller
this standard inline title and
就可以看到
you get a great transition
标准的行内标题
between them and everything's
而且有很好的过渡
looking really great.
看起来很棒
So that's how to use the
这就是如何使用
navigation item properties for
Navigation Item 属性
showing the large title, but I'd
来显示大标题
also like to add search to this
但我还希望给这个 app
application.
添加搜索栏
So I've already gone ahead and
我已经提前
configured a search controller
安装了一个 Search Controller 例子
instance and I just need to show
我希望在这个
the search bar in the
app 里显示
application.
搜索栏
As you may have seen, we're
你可以看到
showing search bars in the
在 iOS 11 里
navigation in iOS 11.
导航栏里会显示搜索栏
So let's add that appearance.
让我们把它加上
If I go over to the memory view
我们再次打开 Memory View Controller
controller again and set the
然后设定
navigation item's search
Navigation Item 的
controller property to our
Search Controller 属性
instance -- in this case it's
在这个例子里
just called "search controller."
就叫 Search Controller
Recompile and rerun the
重新编译
application.
并重启 app
You'll notice when the
你会发现
application comes up into the
app 进入
memory view controller, we still
Memory View Controller 时
have the large title, but now if
还是大标题
we pull down we get this
而当我们下拉时
beautiful new search appearance.
就出现了搜索栏
So this app is looking really
现在这个 app
great.
看起来棒极了
So that's just how to update
这就是如何
some of your bars for the new
更新你的状态栏
appearance in iOS 11.
来显示成 iOS 11 的样子
Now I'd like to bring Kyle
下面请 Kyle Sluder
Sluder up who's going to talk to
来聊一聊
you about margins, insets, and
边缘 嵌入
scroll views.
和 scroll view
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
>> Well done.
>> 干得漂亮
Thank you Raj.
谢谢  Raj
So in iOS 11 we've made a number
在 iOS 11 里
of improvements to give you more
我们做出了不少改进
information and better control
让你们有更多信息
over how your views lay out
也更容易调整 view
their user interfaces.
来展示用户界面
And let's start by talking about
让我们首先说说
layout margins.
布局边缘
Layout margins are a portion of
布局边缘是
the interior of your views that
UI 设计套件中
UI kit gives you as a guide to
为内部 view
layout your content and give a
提供参考的一部分
little breathing room between it
来布局内容
and the surrounding user
给其他的用户界面元素之间
interface elements.
添加一些空间
And we give this information to
我们通过两种方法
you in two ways.
提供信息
The first is a UI layout guide
首先是 UI 布局指导对象
object, which you can use with
你可以和
auto layout to position your
自动布局一起
content.
摆放内容位置
The second is a set of edge
第二种是
insets.
一套边缘内嵌
And you can read these from your
你可以在 view 里
view and write to them to
读取和写入
customize your layout margins.
来个性化布局边缘
In iOS 11 we're adding a new
在 iOS 11 里我们
property; directional layout
添加了一个新属性
margins.
Directional Layout Margins
And this allows you to express
可以让你在 view 里
the layout margins in your
设定布局边缘
views, not just in left and
不只是在左右
right terms, but in leading and
还有前沿
trailing.
和后沿
And these two properties are in
这两个属性
sync with each other.
是相互同步的
The left property is in sync
左属性
with the leading, when you're
和前沿同步
writing in an LTR or left to
当你写入 LTR
right language.
或者从右往左的语言时
And the right property and the
右属性
trailing property are in sync.
和后沿属性同步
So I can do something like write
所以我可以给
a value to the trailing property
这个 view 的后沿属性
of this view, which will cause
写入一个数值
its layout to adjust, and then
使布局调整
when I'm running in a right to
当我写入
left language that trailing
从右往左的语言
space will be put on the left
后沿空间会
side of the view and my layout
出现在 view 左边
code can then read it from the
我的布局代码可以
left property of the layout
从布局边缘的
margin.
左属性读取
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
You may also be familiar with a
有一个性能
behavior that has existed since
在我们一开始介绍
we introduced layout margins
布局边缘时就提到过
where adding a view to a view
当给 View Controller 添加
controller would fix its layout
一个 view 时 可以给
margins to UI kit defined
布局边缘固定一个
values.
UI 设计套件的定义值
Well starting in iOS 11 these
从 iOS 11 开始
are no longer fixed values.
这些将不再是固定数值
They're actually minimums.
而是最小值
And we communicate the size of
我们通过这个新的属性
these values to you with this
System Minimum Layout Margins
new property, system minimum
来定义
layout margins.
这些数值的大小
And you can change your view's
你可以把 view 的
layout margins to any greater
布局边缘数值调大
value, no changes needed.
不需要别的改变
[ Applause ]
[鼓掌]
But we went one step further and
我们又进了一步
we added another new property on
给 View Controller 又添加
view controller; view respects
了一个新的属性
system minimum layout margins.
View Respects System Minimum Layout Margins
If you set this to "false" you
如果设定为 false
can actually change your layout
你可以把布局边缘
margins to whatever value you
改成你想要的任何数值
want, including zero, and you
包括零
can have full width content in
这样在任何 view 里
any view including those that
你都可以得到全幅的内容
are managed by a view
包括那些被
controller.
View Controller 管理的 view
Since iOS 7 we've had these
从 iOS 7 开始
translucent bars throughout the
我们就在操作系统里
operating system and we've
提供这样的半透明的栏
encouraged you to draw your
我们鼓励你把
content through those bars, as
内容拉过这些栏
you can see happening here in
就像我现在
the photos app.
在照片 app 中做的这样
The way that you do this is
之所以有这样的效果
using the edges for extended
是利用 UI View Controller 的
layout property on UI view
属性
controller.
Edges for Extended Layout
And what this does is it causes
它可以让
container view controllers to
Container View Controllers
size your views underneath the
定义这些栏下
bars.
View 的大小
By default it applies to all
默认它适用于
edges and we communicate to you
所有的边缘
the size of the overhanging bars
可以通过两个属性
via these two properties; top
定义悬浮栏的大小
layout guide and bottom layout
Top Layout Guide
guide.
和 bottom Layout Guide
Starting in iOS 11 we're
从 iOS 11 开始
deprecating these properties and
我们舍弃了这些属性
replacing them with a new, more
替换成新的
powerful construct that we call
更强大的架构
the "safe area."
叫安全区域
The safe area is a way of
安全区域是用来
describing the portion of your
描述 view 中
view that isn't occluded by any
没有被内容
content.
占满的部分
It's available to you as a set
你可以通过一套内嵌
of insets or as a UI layout
或者用 UI 布局指导对象
guide object.
来实现
And on TV it incorporates a very
在电视上
useful bit of information called
它嵌入了
the "over scan compensation
一些很有用的信息
insets."
叫 over Scan Compensation Insets
So any view on the screen can
屏幕上的所有 view
layout its content and make sure
都可以布局内容
that it isn't overlapped by the
并确保不会
physical bezel of the
和电视边框
television.
重叠
Now if you have a custom
如果你有
container view controller, you
个性化 Container View Controller
might be adding your own bars
就可以自己添加一些栏
and you can increase the size of
你可以调大
the -- excuse me -- you can
对不起
increase the size of the safe
调大安全区域的嵌入
area insets via this new
通过这个新的属性
property; additional safe area
Additional Safe Area Insets
And if any of your ancestor view
如果你的
controllers change their size of
Ancestor View Controller
their safe area insets you will
改变了安全区域嵌入的大小
get a call back in two different
你可以通过两种方法
ways.
重新掌控主导权
Every view can get safe area
每个 view 都可以
insets to change and view
改变安全区域嵌入
controllers can get view safe
而 View Controllers 也可以
area insets to change.
改变 view 安全区域嵌入
[applause] Thank you.
[ 鼓掌 ] 谢谢
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
So one really common view that's
一个在 UI View Controller 里
used with UI view controller is
经常使用的 view
UI scroll view.
就是 UI scroll view
And in this little sample here I
在这个例子中
have some text that's inside of
我在 UI scroll view 里
the UI scroll view and contained
有一些文字
within a navigation controller.
包含在 Navigation Controller 里
Now traditionally navigation
以前 Navigation Controller
controllers would impart a
会给最高级 View Controller
content inset to the scroll
的 scroll view
views of their topmost view
一个内容内嵌
We're making a really big change
在 iOS 11 里
here in iOS 11 and we're no
我们做出了很大的改变
longer populating the content
我们不再
inset property through scroll
通过 scroll view
views.
填入内容内嵌属性
Instead we've added a new
我们添加了
property, adjusted content
一个新属性
inset, that includes the sum of
Adjusted Content Inset
the content inset and any
包括内容内嵌的总和
overlap from container view
和其他 Container View Controller
controllers.
的重叠
This means you can use the
这意味着你可以用
content inset property for
内容内嵌属性
whatever purposes are
来对 app 进行
appropriate for your
你希望的任何改进
application, such as this
例如这个
additional information about
文字的附加信息
this text here, and we won't
我们不会
change it.
改变它
And you don't have to worry
而且你不需要考虑
about saving and restoring any
保存和恢复
UI kit provided values and
任何 UI 设计套件提供的数值
having content underlapping
或者害怕内容覆盖
navigation bars or the status
导航栏
bar.
或者状态栏
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
You may be familiar with our
你可能知道
auto layout support in UI scroll
UI scroll view 里
view that lets you dictate how
自动布局的支持
big the scrollable region of
让你可以通过
your scroll view is by
把 sub-view
constraining sub-views to the
约束到 scroll view
scroll view itself.
来决定可滚动范围的大小
And we've added a couple of UI
我们添加了
layout guide objects that make
一些 UI 布局指导对象
your layout more clear and more
可以让你的布局
expressive and more powerful.
更清楚更强大
The first is a UI layout guide
第一个是
object called the frame layout
Frame Layout guide
And this layout guide
这个布局指导
corresponds to the position and
负责 scroll view
size of your scroll view in
在屏幕中的大小和位置
screen space, which means you
也就是说
can do things like constrain the
你可以约束 sub-view
sub-view, like this page
就像这个
indicator, and it will stay
页面指示器
fixed on screen as the user
当用户滑动页面时
scrolls.
它就会固定在屏幕上
The second layout guide object
第二个布局指导对象
we've added is the content
是这个
layout guide.
Content Layout Guide
And you can contain your
你可以约束 sub-view
sub-views in order to influence
来控制 scroll view 中
the scrollable size of your
可滚动的区域大小
scroll view or have things move
或者让内容
as the user scrolls.
随着滚动而移动
One really common sub class of
一个很常见的 UI scroll view
UI scroll view is UI table view
的子类别是 UI table view
and we've made a number of
我们对它也作出了
changes here too, the biggest of
一些改变  其中最大的是
which is that table views use
table view 会默认
self-sizing by default on iOS
以 iOS 11 自主调节大小
11, not on TVOS.
而不是  tvOS
This means that your headers,
等于说  你的页眉
your footers, and your cells are
页脚和单元
using estimated sizes.
使用的是  预估大小
We've done this by changing the
我们把 UI table view
default value of the estimated
预估大小属性
size properties on UI table view
的默认值
to this constant, automatic
变成这个恒定的
dimension.
自动尺寸
This means that you need to
所以你要
ensure that your cells all have
确保单元有
sufficient internal constraints
足够的内部约束
to tell UI table view how big
来决定 UI table view 的大小
they should be or you need to
或者你可以
implement the delegate methods
执行委托方法
that tell us how big your rows
告诉我们行距
are.
有多大
You should also implement those
对于页眉和页脚
delicate methods for you headers
也应该执行
and your footers.
这些方法
Now maybe you want to link your
也许你想把 app
application against the iOS 11
链接到 iOS 11 SDK
SDK, but you're not ready to
但是你不打算
adopt this new behavior.
采取这个新性能
You can opt out of it by setting
你可以取消它
the estimated height properties
通过把 table view 的预估高度属性
on your table views to zero.
调成零
That will turn off estimated
这样就可以取消
sizes, which will also disable
预估大小  同时也使
self-sizing.
自动调节大小失效
Now you may be familiar with
还有另外一个概念
another concept we introduced a
我们刚才介绍过
And this is a portion of your
它是 view 的一部分
views that if you lay out your
如果把
content within, will be
内容布局在里面
comfortable to read even on a
看起来就很舒服
large device like an iPad in
哪怕是在一些较大的设备上
landscape.
比如横屏的 ipad 上
Now by default table views have
默认情况下  table view
a separator inset that is within
在可读内容区域
the readable content area and
有分隔符内嵌
this influences the position of
可以影响
the separators and of the labels
分隔符和
in the table use content view
table view 里标签
itself.
的位置
And if you change the separator
如果改变
insets' values you would see
分隔符内嵌的数值
that the separator inset moves
可以看到分隔符内嵌
relative to its readable content
随之移动到
guide position.
可读内容的相应的位置
Starting in iOS 11 we're
从 iOS 11 开始
changing this and the separator
我们做出了调整
insets will always be relative
分隔符内嵌会一直和
to the edges of the cells
单元自己的边缘相关
themselves, which are the full
也就是 table view
width of the table view, which
的全屏宽度
means you can set these values
你可以把数值设为零
to zero and have full width,
就可以看到
full bleed content even on an
全幅内容
iPad running in landscape.
即使针对横屏时的 iPad
And this is a table view on an
这是 iPhone 的 table view
iPhone and if I change the
如果我在这调整
separator inset here you can see
分隔符内嵌
that it is also defined relative
你可以看到
to the edges of the cell -- to
单元和 table view 的边缘
the edge of the table view.
也随之改变
We've added a new property to UI
我们给 UI table view
table view, separator inset
添加了一个新属性
reference, that you can use to
Separator Inset Reference
tell us that you actually just
你可以用它
want to adjust the separator
把分隔符内嵌
inset from its default automatic
从默认的自动位置上
position.
加以改变
And this works on iPad too.
这个在 iPad 上也适用
A couple of things to keep in
有几件事情要注意
mind about the way the table
关于 table view
views interact with the safe
是如何与安全区域交互的
area; those automatic separator
这些自动分隔符内嵌
insets are relative to the safe
和安全区域内嵌
area insets.
是相关的
So by default the entire content
所以我们默认
of your table view avoids the
table view 的全部内容
safe area insets from its
在安全内边距内
ancestor view controllers.
避开它的
UI table view cell and UI table
UI Table View Cell 和
view header/footer view, which
UI Table View Header Footer View
might be one of the longer names
这可能是设计套件里
in the kit, they both have a
最长的名字了
content view property.
他们都有一个 content view 属性
That's where you should be
你应该在这里
adding your sub-views.
添加 sub-view
Both of these classes make sure
这两个类可以
that that content view also
确保 content view
avoids the safe area insets.
也可以避开安全区域嵌入
So you should be using UI table
所以你应该在你的 table view 的
view header/footer view for all
所有的页眉和页脚
of the headers and footers in
使用 UI Table View Header Footer View
your table views; table headers
表格页眉页脚
and footers and section headers
还有章节页眉
and footers.
和页脚
We've also brought over the
我们还从邮件 app 里
really rich swipe action
借鉴了很多
functionality from the mail
滑动操作功能
application to your
为你们的 app
applications.
服务
will get the new swipe action
会有新的默认的
look and feel by default, and if
滑动操作
you link against iOS 11, you can
如果你用了 iOS 11
get full swipe to delete
就可以使用滑动删除
behavior, just like you're used
就像以前在
to from the mail app.
邮件里一样
And if you go ahead --
如果你
[applause] some people are very
[ 鼓掌 ] 我知道有些人
excited about this I know.
很喜欢这个
[applause] And if you go ahead
[ 鼓掌 ] 如果你
and adopt a few new APIs you can
采用一些新的 API
get some really cool features,
就可以得到一些很棒的功能
like images in your swipe
像滑动操作的图像
actions, or swipe actions from
从前沿和后沿
both the leading and the
滑动
trailing edges, or a completion
或者一个完成处理器
handler that lets you cancel the
让你可以取消
swipe action.
滑动操作
And to show us how to adopt all
如何在我们的 app
these features in our
里采用这些功能
application, Raj is going to
Raj会上来
come up and give us another
给我们进行
demo.
演示
Raj?
Raj
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
>> Thanks Kyle.
>> 谢谢  Kyle
So we're going to switch over to
让我们重新转到
the demo machine again and as
演示设备上来
you can see we've got these big
你可以看到
beautiful bars in this new
这个 app 里的
application.
这些漂亮的栏
It's looking really great.
看起来很棒
But I want to show you the
我想要向你们展示
comments view controller.
Comments View Controller
Now if I push into the comments
如果我点进这个
notice we have some really
你可以看到这些
interesting comments and we've
有趣的评论
got all the comments here in a
所有的这些评论
comment bar at the bottom.
都在下面的评论栏里
Now our users have been asking
我们的用户
us for one thing and that's time
想要一样东西
stamps.
就是  时码
And so I went and spoke to our
所以我告诉了我们的设计师
designer and got this really
然后他们提供了
cool design for this awesome new
这个超赞的
scroll bar.
滚动栏的设计
This scroll bar also indicates,
这个滚动栏不仅
not only where you are in the
标识出你在
comments view, but also the time
Comment view 里的位置
stamp where it's pointing.
还有它所在的时码
So let's go ahead and implement
现在我们来
that.
操作一下
I'll switch over to the comments
我现在转到
view controller and create our
Comments View Controller
scroll bar using a method I
然后用我之前写的一个方法
wrote earlier.
来新建一个滚动栏
And when I recompile and rerun
当我重新编译并重启
the application, scroll down,
往下滑
tap on one of these cells, and
点击这些单元中的一个
into the comments view
并进入到 Comments View Controller
controller you'll see there it
你就可以看得它了
is.
看起来很棒吧
It shows you where you are in
它显示出你在
this comments view controller
Comments View Controller 中的位置
and the time stamp of the cell
和它所指向的单元
that it's pointing at.
的时码
But, as you might notice, there
但是也许你注意到了
are a few issues here.
还存在一些问题
The first issue is that this
首先是
indicator actually overlaps with
这个指示器会稍微遮挡一点
the table view cell a little bit
这个 table view 单元
and so it makes things maybe a
所以看起来
little bit hard to read.
会有点不清楚
The second thing is that this
第二就是
indicator overlaps with this
这个指示器会遮挡
input field here at the bottom.
下边的输入区域
So let's use some new APIs in
所以让我们用一些 iOS 11 里的
iOS 11 to help solve these
新的 API
problems.
来解决这些问题
We're going to use the
我们会用到
additional safe area insets
UI View Controller 的
property on UI view controller
Additional Safe Area Insets 属性
to help solve this.
来解决这个问题
So I'll go ahead and unwrap our
所以我现在
two views and I'll set our
打开这两个 view
additional safe area insets to a
把 additional Safe Area Insets
UA edge insets.
添加给 UI 边缘内嵌
So on the top we don't have
所以  上面
anything additional to add.
我们不添加任何东西
On the left that's the same
左边
story.
也是一样
On the bottom we want to make it
下面  我们要把它
the comment bar's size.
变成评论栏的大小
So we'll get the height of the
所以我们输入
comment bar and on the right we
评论栏的高度
have a property that I've
右边有个属性
written earlier on the side
是我之前给指示器写好的
indicator that gives its
让它有
preferred width.
合适的宽度
So now we've set up our
我们设定好
additional safe area insets.
Additional Safe Area Insets
If I recompile and rerun the
重新编译并重启
detail view and again into the
打开 detail view
comments view controller, you'll
然后进入 Comments View Controller
notice things are starting to
你会发现
look pretty good.
看起来好多了
We've got our content inset from
我们把内容
the right edge and the scroll
从右边缘嵌入
indicator's also inset from the
滚动指示器也从下边缘嵌入
bottom edge, but you'll notice
你会发现
here, down at the bottom, that
在下边
this comment field actually is
这个评论区域
inset a little bit from the
从屏幕右边
right edge of the screen.
嵌入了一点
So the reason for that is the
原因是
comment field's text field is
评论区域的文字区
constrained to its super views
被限制到它的
layout margins.
super view 布局边缘中了
Now in iOS 11 your layout
在 iOS 11 里
margins are actually inset from
布局边缘是
the safe area and because we
嵌入安全区域的  因为我们
added additional safe area
在 view 的右边
insets on the right of this view
添加了 additional Safe Area Insets
our layout margins get inset
所以布局边缘
accordingly.
也相应嵌入
Now most of the time this is
大部分时候
going to be exactly what you
这就是你想要的效果
want, but we do have a property
但是我们
on UI view, "insets layout
还有另外一个属性
margins from safe area," which
Insets Layout Margins From Safe Area
lets you control this property.
让你可以控制这个属性
So for this use case let's go
在这个例子里
ahead and set that to "false."
让我们把这个属性设定为false
When I go ahead and do that,
如果我这么做了
recompile and rerun the
重新编译并重启 app
application, go back into the
然后进入到
detail view controller and
Detail View Controller
finally into the comments view
然后再进入 Comments View Controller
controller, you'll see things
你会发现
are starting to look really
看起来很不错
We've got our content at the
评论出现在
right spot.
合适的位置
We've got our beautiful new
新的滚动指示器
scroll indicator.
也在
Everything is inset and the
所有都嵌入了
comment field is a full width.
评论区也有全屏宽
Awesome! The next thing I'd like
赞  接下来
to show you is adding swipe
我要展示  给这个 app
actions to this application.
添加滑动操作
So I've decided that I'd like to
如果我想
add the ability to favorite and
收藏
maybe delete some of these
或者删除
things.
一些东西
So let's go to the memory view
那让我们进入 Memory View Controller
controller and add support for
然后在 iOS 11 里
the new swipe actions in iOS 11.
给这个新滑动操作添加支持
So it looks like a lot, but I'll
看起来好像很复杂
walk you through it.
但是我会告诉你怎么做
All I've done is implemented two
我执行了两个新方法
new methods; leading swipe
前沿滑动操作配置
actions configuration for road
索引路径
indexpath and trailing swipe
和后沿
actions configurations for road
滑动操作配置
indexpath.
索引路径
So let's walk through the
我们先来看看
leading one.
前沿的这个
All I do is I create a UI
创建一个
contextual action here, with a
UI 情景动作
style of "normal," a title of
样式选为 normal
"favorite," and a block based
标题是  收藏
handler.
还有一个分块处理器
I update our favorites state,
把收藏状态更新
using a method I wrote earlier,
用我之前写好的一个代码
and then I call the completion
把完成处理器
handler with the parameter of
的参数设为
"true."
true
Just so everything's looking
为了让一切都看起来没问题
right, I'll also set it to
我再把它设定为  取消收藏
"unfavorite," based on whether
取决于这个条目
that item's already favorited.
是否已经被收藏
And then I'll set the image to
然后设置
this beautiful star that I had
这个我之前做好的
made earlier and the background
星星图标
color to this awesome looking
背景色选为漂亮的
orange.
橙色
And then all I need to do is
接下来只需要
create a UI swipe actions
创建一个 UI 滑动操作配置
configuration using that UI
用 UI 情景动作
contextual action and return it.
然后归还
The story's pretty much the same
后沿动作
for the trailing actions; I just
也差不多
use the style of disruptive.
我只是把样式选成 disruptive
So when I recompile and rerun
重新编译并重启
this time, go back over, and
进入然后滑动
swipe, you'll notice we get this
可以注意到
option swipe actions and you can
有了选项滑动操作
even have a swipe action on the
在前沿可以出现
leading edge, as you see here,
滑动操作  就像这样
which you were never able to do
以前完全做不到
For full -- furthermore, you get
还有
full swipe to delete support out
可以滑动
of the box.
把这个条目删除
So all I need to do is swipe all
只要
the way across and it just
整体滑过去
works.
就可以了
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
So that's a look at some of the
这就是关于  边缘
new APIs for margins, insets,
嵌入  scroll view
scroll views, and bars in this
还有栏的新 API
demo app.
的演示
It's looking really great and
看起来很棒
definitely ready for iOS 11.
而且绝对适合 iOS 11
Now Kyle's going to come back up
接下来 Kyle 会再度登台
to tell you about some related
为大家介绍相关
sessions.
内容
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
>> Thank you again Raj.
>> 再次谢谢 Raj
So just to recap what we've
复习一下今天的内容
learned today; we've learned how
我们学习了
to adopt large navigation titles
采用大导航标题
and the new integrated search
和新融入的
experience into our applications
搜索栏
for iOS 11.
在 iOS 11 里
We've also learned about some
我们还学习了
new improvements to layout
布局边缘的
margins that give us complete
新改进  让我们可以
control over our views and the
完全掌控
way they layout, as well as a
View 和布局
new concept called the safe
还有一个叫做
area, which tells us about
安全区域的新概念
overlapping contents and things
是关于内容覆盖的
like over scan compensation
比如在 Apple TV 上
insets on Apple TV.
嵌入扫描补偿
We've learned about some new
我们学习了
enhancements to UI scroll view
UI scroll view 的改进功能
that give us better control over
让我们可以
our content inset and some new
更好的控制内容嵌入
features in UI table view and
还有 UI table view 的新性能
how it interacts with concepts
以及它如何跟安全区域
like the safe area.
之类的内容互动
If you have more questions be
如果你还有更多的问题
sure to visit the site for this
请访问这个课程
session.
的网址
Have a great WWDC.
希望你们享受 WWDC